{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"4.318/1.7",
			"answer":"4.318/1.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.5828/9.4",
			"answer":"0.5828/9.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"92.61/4.9",
			"answer":"92.61/4.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"366.7/0.19",
			"answer":"366.7/0.19",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.039/1.3",
			"answer":"0.039/1.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3430/3.5",
			"answer":"3430/3.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"381.9/3.5",
			"answer":"381.9/3.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9.348/8.2",
			"answer":"9.348/8.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.3655/0.043",
			"answer":"0.3655/0.043",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"573.4/6.1",
			"answer":"573.4/6.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}